{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What date does Bunzo Cutout say in Chapter 2?",
            "options": ["June 28th", "April 1st", "August 18th", "January 26th"],
            "answer": "June 28th"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different colors does Musical Memory have?",
            "options": ["5", "7", "4", "6"],
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different Train Codes are there?",
            "options": ["4", "256", "10", "64"],
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many colors you need to hit to open the door leading to the Blue Hand in Chapter 1?",
            "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many times you need to hit Mini-Huggies in order to complete Whack-A-Wuggy?",
            "options": ["25", "30", "35", "40"],
            "answer": "40"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different tapes are in Chapter 1?",
            "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different tapes are in Chapter 2?",
            "options": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different tapes are in Chapter 3?",
            "options": ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
            "answer": "11"
        },
        {
            "question": "What trick involves NAM Skip?",
            "options": ["Hyperspeed Swing", "Prop Boost", "Jump Buffer", "Green Hand Early"],
            "answer": "Hyperspeed Swing"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different Deaths are there in Chapter 2?",
            "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different Cutouts are there in Chapter 2?",
            "options": ["7", "8", "9", "10"],
            "answer": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many different Cutouts are there in Chapter 3?",
            "options": ["9", "10", "11", "12"],
            "answer": "12"
        }
    ]
}
